I think social media
is on the cusp of the biggest change it's
had in a very
long time.
And if people don't make the necessary
steps to look at social media a
certain way,
they're going to get left behind.
We have AI on the horizon.
We have more people than ever creating
content.
And whereas some of us, including myself,
were very early in our niches to get
online and create a personal brand,
people are now realizing now
is the time to do
it.
Where some people relied heavily on paid
ads and some people relied heavily on
other traditional forms of marketing,
now people have started to realize that if
they do not come front
and center of their business
and do exactly what I'm doing
now,
their businesses will get left behind,
and they will not survive.
Now,
I am in the process of building a system
to help everyone that I
work with move to longer form content.
Google released a study a few years ago
saying that the average person needs to
spend seven hours in front of you.
And I've been mulling it over for a while.
I've spent a bit of time with Daniel
Priestley, who I have huge admiration for.
Out of all the business gurus online,
I'm going to throw it out there, I watch
their content and think to myself,
"This person's chatting shit."
But for some
reason, well, actually no,
for good reason,
when I listen to Daniel Priestley, I'm
like, "Do you know what?
I really agree with that."
Or he will say things and I go,
"Do you know what? I've thought
that for years,
but I didn't have a word for it."
And he has his 11-seven-four principle,
which mimics
very much what I've been saying in my live
shows about trying to get seven hours in
front of people.
But he says it should be on different
platforms.
I completely agree.